Finding Aid for Arthur J. Tuttle Papers 1849-1958
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Topical Office Files
  - August 1933-July 1937
    - Federal Building-Detroit (Box 33)
      (Construction Engineer Scott Fullerton, Cafeteria Committee Chair Charles R. Dickson)
    - Federal Judges (Box 33)
      (Judges Edward J. Moinet, Ernest A. O'Brien, Arthur F. Lederle, John Knight, George P. Hahn, Charles C. Simons, Patrick T. Stone, Fred M. Raymond, Albert L. Reeves, Isaac M. Meekins, Guy A. Miller, Richard J. Hopkins, Xen Hicks, Walter C. Lindley, Charles Moorman, John C. Knox, John J. Gore; Congressmen J.C. Lehr, Clarence J. McLeod, John D. Dingell)
    - Forms-Equity Cases (Box 33)
    - Frazier-Lemke Amendment (Box 33)
      (Congressmen Roy O. Woodworth, Fred L. Crawford; letters from public)
    - Furniture & Carpets for New Federal Building (Box 33)
      (2 blueprints with floor plans of 7th floor Detroit Federal Building 10/15/31 and undated)
    - G-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 33)
      (Letter describing the new décor at the Bay City offices of Tuttle, including deer heads.)
    - H-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 33)
    - I-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 33)
    - Internal Revenue Service (Box 33)
    - J-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 33)
    - Jurors (Box 34)
      (Alma Lutz of National Woman's Party about women jurors; invitations to jurors' reunions, people begging to be put on juror list)
    - K-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 34)
    - L-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 34)
      (Congressman David J. Lewis)
    - Law Clerk, appointment of (Box 34)
      (U of M Law Dean Henry M. Bates, Judges C. H. Moorman, A. F. Lederle, Clerk Donald L. Quaife, Cong. Clarence J. McLeod, Atty. Gen'l Homer Cummings, Asst. Atty Gen'l Joseph B Keenan)
    - M-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 34)
      (Cong. Clarence J. McLeod, William W. Blackney, Pres. Michigan Bar Ass'n Roy E. Brownell)
    - Moinet, Hon. Edward J. (Box 34)
    - Migratory Bird Hunting Stamp Act (Box 34)
      (Funny correspondence in which Tuttle snipes at New Deal legislation regulating hunting licenses for migratory birds. Asks U of M's Louis Bredvold, English Dept. chair for help construing the prose, 1937)
    - Moorman, Hon. Charles H. (Box 34)
    - N-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 34)
    - Narcotics (Box 34)
    - Naturalization Matters (Box 34)
      (Congressman Roy Woodruff)
    - New Court Rules (Box 34)
      (Pres. Detroit Bar Assn. George E. Brand, Judge Charles H. Moorman)
    - O-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 34)
    - O'Brien, Hon. Ernest A. (Box 34)
      (Pres. Detroit Bar Assn. George E. Brand, Pres. Mich. Bar Assn. Roy E. Brownell, Pres. Wayne Co. Bar Assn. Aldrich Baxter, Congressman Earl C. Michener regarding threatened impeachment of O'Brien)
    - P-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 34)
    - Probation Officer, Appointment of (Box 34)
      (Supervisor U.S. Probation System Col. Joel R. Moore, Detroit Chief Probation Officer Richard F. Doyle)
    - Probation Dept. (Box 34)
      (Col. Joel R. Moore, Detroit Chief Probation Officer L. Wallace Hoffman)
    - Probation Dept. Annual Reports (Box 34)
    - Probation Matters-Local and National (Box 34)
      (Col. Joel R. Moore, L. Wallace Hoffman)
    - Prohibition Matters-Employees (Box 34)
      (Judge helps find employment for officers after repeal of prohibition)
    - Psychiatric Advisor (Box 34)
    - Q-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 34)
    - R-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 34)
    - Requisitions and Travel Expenses (Box 34)
    - Speech-Rotary International (Box 34)
    - S-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 34)
      (Series of letters corresponding between Congressman Hoffman and Tuttle regarding the sentencing and disbarment of Maurice Sugar for draft evasion. He had been the lawyer for the CIO.)
    - Standing Master, Appointment of (Box 34)
    - T-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 34)
    - Tuttle, Arthur-JMB
      (Daily correspondence between Tuttle and his secretary)
      - 1933 (Box 34)
      - 1934 (Box 34)
      - 1935 (Box 35)
      - 1936 (Box 35)
      - 1937 (Box 35)
    - U-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 35)
    - U.S. Attorney (Box 35)
      (Detroit U.S. Atty. Gregory H. Frederick, Assts. William G. Comb, Ken F. Corbitt, Francis X. Norris, Atty. Walter I. McKenzie re: U.S. Attorney in Bay City)
    - U.S. Commissioners (Box 35)
      (Lansing Comr. Thomas J. Bailey, Jr., Detroit Comr. Frank Q. Quinn)
    - U.S. Commissioners, Appointment of (Box 35)
      (J. Edgar Hoover, FBI investigative report regarding Detroit U.S. Commissioners)
    - U.S. Marshals (Box 35)
    - V-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 35)
    - W-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 35)
      (Congressman Roy O. Woodruff)
  - August 1937-1944
    - A-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 35)
      (Attorney General Francis Biddle)
    - Administrative Office of the U.S. Courts
      (Director Henry P. Chandler, Asst. Director Elmore Whitehurst, Chief of Statistics Will Shafroth)
      - 1940 (Box 35)
      - 1941 (Box 35)
      - January-June 1942 (Box 35)
      - July-December 1942 (Box 35)
      - 1943 (Box 35)
      - 1944 (Box 35)
      - Bulletins (Box 35)
    - B-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 35)
    - Bankruptcy
      (George Marston, Paul King, Walter I. McKenzie)
      - Attorneys' Fees (Box 35)
      - Miscellaneous
        - 1937 (Box 35)
        - 1938 (Box 35)
        - 1939 (Box 36)
        - 1940 (Box 36)
        - 1941 (Box 36)
        - 1942 (Box 36)
        - 1943 (Box 36)
          (Death of Paul King, appointment of McKenzie)
        - 1944 (Box 36)
      - Not Court (Box 36)
      - Office Administration
        - 1937-1938 (Box 36)
        - 1939 (Box 36)
        - 1940-1944 (Box 36)
      - Referee's Appointment (Box 36)
      - Requisitions and Reports
        - 1937 (Box 36)
        - 1938 (Box 36)
        - 1939 (Box 36)
        - 1940 (Box 36)
        - 1941 (Box 36)
        - 1942 (Box 36)
        - 1943-1944 (Box 36)
      - Rules (Box 36)
    - C-Miscellaneous Correspondence, 2 folders (Box 37)
      (Judge Charles N. Pray)
    - Chandler Bill (pending) (Box 37)
      (Judge Arthur F. Lederle, Congressman Hutton W. Summers, Pres. Fed. Bar Assn. Henry Ward Beer)
    - Clerk of Court-Bay City
      - 1937 (Box 37)
      - 1938 (Box 37)
      - 1939 (Box 37)
      - 1940 (Box 37)
      - 1941 (Box 37)
      - 1942 (Box 37)
      - 1943 (Box 37)
      - 1944 (Box 37)
    - Clerk of Court-Detroit
      - Jury Record (Box 37)
      - 1937-1938 (Box 37)
        (Report conducted by the Department of Justice about mismanagement of the Clerks office and a plan to improve it, October 28, 1937. Voorhees resigned in disgrace.)
      - 1939-1940 (Box 37)
      - 1941-1942 (Box 37)
      - 1943-1944 (Box 37)
    - Committee on Rules of Criminal Procedure (Box 37)
    - Court Reporter (Box 37)
      (Judges Albert B. Maris, John J. Parker, Merrill E. Otis, Congressman Earl C. Michener)
    - Court Rules, 2 folders (Box 37)
      (Judge Fred M. Raymond, John Clark Knox, Atty. Harold H. Smedley, Atty. George E. Brand, Judges H. Church Ford, Xenophon Hicks, Clerk of Circuit Court John W. Menzies, Detroit U.S. Attorney John C. Lehr. Tuttle was chair of circuit-wide committee on district court rules)
    - Custodian (Box 37)
    - D-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 37)
      (Author Lucille Disenroth)
    - Department of Justice
      - 1937-1938 (Box 37)
        (Attys. General Frank Murphy, Homer Cummings, Admin. Asst. to Atty. General T.D. Quinn, Special Attorney for Lands Division Jules Kabatsky (letter very critical of condemnation procedures))
      - 1939 (Box 37)
    - District Court Judges (Box 38)
      (Judges Edward J. Moinet, Ernest A. O'Brien, Arthur F. Lederle, Frank A. Picard, Hiram Church Ford, John D. Martin, Fred M. Raymond, William J. Campbell (re: Max Stephan), Shackelford Miller, Jr.)
      - 1937-1940 (Box 38)
      - 1941-1942 (Box 38)
      - 1943 (Box 38)
      - 1944 (Box 38)
    - Docket, Statistics
      - 1939 (Box 38)
      - 1940 (Box 38)
      - 1941-1942, 2 folders (Box 38)
      - 1943 (Box 38)
      - 1944 (Box 38)
    - E-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 38)
    - F-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 38)
    - Federal Bureau of Investigation (Box 38)
      (J. Edgar Hoover, Agent John S. Bugas)
    - G-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 38)
      (Judge Nelson McVicar)
    - Grant, Miss Eula (Box 38)
    - H-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 38)
    - Habeas Corpus (Box 38)
      (Director Henry P. Chandler, Clerk George M. Read)
    - Hicks, Hon. Xenophon (Box 38)
    - I-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 38)
    - Indeterminate Sentence (Box 38)
      (Director Henry P. Chandler, Leland L. Tolman of Administrative Office)
    - J-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 38)
      (Chief Probation Officer Richard F. Doyle, Congressman Earl Michener)
    - Judge, Additional Federal (Box 38)
      (Congressman John D. Dingell)
    - Judicial Conference May 1941 (Box 38)
    - Judiciary, Congressional Committee on (Box 38)
      (30 page letter to Congressman Hatton W. Summers with copies to many Members of Congress, letters acknowledging receipt)
    - Jurors (Box 38)
      (Judges John McDuffie, John C. Knox)
    - Grand Jury-Bay City (May, 1940) (Box 39)
    - Traverse Jury-Bay City May, 1940 (Box 39)
    - K-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 39)
      (Judge Eugene J. Keogh)
    - L-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 39)
    - Law Clerk (Box 39)
    - M-Miscellaneous Correspondence I (Box 39)
      (Congressman Earl C. Michener, Attorney General Frank Murphy, Judge Albert B. Maris)
    - M-Miscellaneous Correspondence II (Box 39)
    - Milan U.S. Detention Farm (Box 39)
    - Moorman, Hon. Charles (Box 39)
    - N-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 39)
    - Naturalization
      (Tuttle speech, September 7, 1939, Congressman George G. Sadowski, Lieut. Gov. Leo J. Nowicki, Naturalization Examiner Robert C. Wilson, Asst. District Directors INS Andrew Jordan, Paul G. Werner)
      - 1937-1939 (Box 39)
      - 1940-1941 (Box 39)
      - 1942 (Box 39)
      - 1943-1944 (Box 39)
      - Memoranda December 15, 1942 (Box 39)
    - O-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 39)
    - Office of Price Administration (Box 39)
      (Bowles suit)
    - P-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 39)
      (Prof. Alfred White (Chemical Engineering), Judges Orie L. Phillips, John J. Parker)
    - Patents (Box 39)
      (Congressman Frank W. Boykin)
    - Probation
      (Chief Probation Officer Richard F. Doyle, Bay City Officer Rudolph E. Boehringer, Director Bureau of Prisons James V. Bennett, Supervisor U.S. Courts Probation System Richard F. Chappell, Pardon Attorney DOJ Daniel M. Lyons, Congressman Hatton W. Sumners)
      - 1937-1939 (Box 39)
      - 1940-1941 (Box 39)
      - 1942-1944 (Box 39)
    - Probation Officers, Draft status of (Box 39)
      (Director Henry P. Chandler, Judge D. Lawrence Groner)
    - Quaife, Donald L. (Law clerk and special master) (Box 39)
    - R-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 39)
    - Requisitions, Travel Vouchers, 2 folders (Box 39)
    - Rules of Criminal Procedure (Box 40)
      (Profs. C.B. Hilberry (Wayne U.), Louis I. Bredvold (U of M), David Worcester (Mich. State), Congressman Eugene J. Keogh, Hatton W. Judges Fred M. Raymond, Director Henry P. Chandler)
    - S-Miscellaneous Correspondence, 2 folders (Box 40)
      (Judges Charles C. Simons, D. Lawrence Groner)
    - Salaries (Box 40)
      (Congressmen Chauncey W. Reed, Director Henry P. Chandler)
    - T-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 40)
    - Transportation (Naturalization Class) (Box 40)
    - Tuttle, Arthur-JMB
      - 1937 (Box 40)
      - 1938 (Box 40)
      - 1939 (Box 40)
      - 1940 (Box 40)
      - 1941 (Box 40)
      - 1942 (Box 40)
      - 1943 (Box 40)
      - 1944 (Box 40)
    - U-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 40)
    - U.S. Attorney at Bay City (Box 40)
      (Atty. Gen. Homer Cummings, Assts. to Atty. General Matthew F. McGuire, Joseph B. Keenan, Senator Prentiss Brown, Director Henry P. Chandler)
    - U.S. Attorneys (Box 40)
      (Detroit U.S. Attorney John C. Lehr, Assts. Francis X. Norris, John W. Babcock, J. Thomas Smith, Thomas P. Thornton, John Ray, Peter P. Gilbert, Vincent Fordell, Kenneth D. Wilkins)
    - U.S. Commissioner (Box 40)
      (Bay City Cmr. Otto J. Manary)
    - U.S. Marshal (Box 40)
      (John J. Barc)
    - V-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 40)
    - W-Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 40)
      (Congressman Roy O. Woodruff, Judges Thomas A.E. Weadock, Samuel H. West)
    - W.P.A Project-American Law Institute Annotations (Box 41)
      - 1938 (Box 41)
        (N.J. Atty. Gen. David T. Wilentz, WPA managers Charles J. Fellrath, Harold A. Johnson, ALI official George B. Hurff, Jr., NY Atty. Gen. John J. Bennett, Jr., Mich. Atty. Gen. Raymond W. Starr, Pres. Detroit Bar Assn. Paul Weadock)
      - 1939 (Box 41)
        (Asst. to U.S. Atty. Gen. T.D. Quinn, Detroit WPA officials Elizabeth R. Donnelly, Abner Larned, Asst. Director WPA Howard Hunter, Thelma Fasbinder)
      - 1940 (Box 41)
        (WPA project supervisor James S. Kennary)
      - 1941 (Box 41)
        (Asst. Director Elmore Whitehurst)
      - 1942-1944 (Box 41)
        (WPA official Dorothy K. Roosevelt)
- Conciliation Commissioners
  The Conciliation commissioners series (.7 linear feet) contains the records of an odd era in American Bankruptcy Law under the Frazier-Lemke Law whereby farmer debtors could appear before a county conciliation commissioner (usually a non-lawyer) and their creditors to try to force an agreement about the distribution of their assets. It was not very successful. These files contain the records of Tuttle's appointments of the various county commissioners and his correspondence with them.
  (Frazier-Lemke Law re Farmer-Debtors, 1934-1935
  - Alpena County (Box 41)
    (George A. St. Charles)
  - Alcona County (Box 41)
    (William T. Miller)
  - Arenac County (Box 41)
    (Grover C. Spencer)
  - Bay County (Box 41)
    (Richard F. Macey)
  - Branch County (Box 41)
    (Charles G. Somerlott)
  - Calhoun County (Box 41)
    (Frank Gauss)
  - Conciliation Commissioners, Miscellaneous (Box 41)
    (Directors Mich. Bureau of Agricultural Industry A.C. Carton, Paul van Deinse, form letters)
  - Conciliation Commission, Miscellaneous Circulars (Box 41)
    (Local rules from many jurisdictions)
  - Conciliation Commission, Court Rules Various Districts (Box 41)
    (Under Secs. 75 and 77b of Bankruptcy Act)
  - Cheboygan County (Box 41)
    (Allan F. Gerow)
  - Clare County (Box 41)
    (Joseph Murphy)
  - Clinton County (Box 41)
    (Verne Hand)
  - Crawford County (Box 41)
    (Herbert A. Ferguson)
  - Genesee County (Box 41)
    (James T. Sullivan)
  - Gladwin County (Box 41)
    (Nathan A. Grey)
  - Gratiot County (Box 41)
    (Harry Gulick)
  - Hillsdale County (Box 41)
    (Guy Reppert)
  - Huron County (Box 41)
    (Peter Campbell)
  - Ingham County (Box 41)
    (William A. Blackmore)
  - Iosco County (Box 41)
    (William H. Phelps, Emil Christenson)
  - Isabella County (Box 41)
    (Earle Johnson)
  - Jackson County (Box 41)
    (Ora E. Garred)
  - Lapeer County (Box 41)
    (James J. Porter)
  - Lenawee County (Box 41)
    (Mrs. Delia Rhoads)
  - Livingston County (Box 41)
    (Jay Barber)
  - Macomb County (Box 41)
    (Joshua B. Immen)
  - Midland County (Box 41)
    (Ray J. Gilson)
  - Monroe County (Box 41)
    (Otto Russow)
  - Montmorency County (Box 41)
    (Theodore Bouchey, Mrs. Cora A. Tracy)
  - Oakland County (Box 41)
    (Mrs. Cecil A. Ingamills)
  - Ogemaw County (Box 41)
    (Mrs. Cora Richardson)
  - Oscoda County (Box 41)
    (Elmer J. Handrick)
  - Otsego County (Box 41)
    (David G. Fleming)
  - Presque Isle County (Box 41)
    (Adelbert P. Bertram)
  - Roscommon County (Box 41)
    (Mrs. Justine Richardson)
  - Saginaw County (Box 41)
    (Mrs. Emma Marnien)
  - Shiawassee County (Box 41)
    (Gershon E. Mattoon)
  - Sanilac County (Box 41)
    (Mrs. Anna May Balhoff)
  - St. Clair County (Box 41)
    (Earl C. Diem)
  - Tuscola County (Box 41)
    (Charles Lockhart)
  - Washtenaw County (Box 41)
    (Leo A. Guinan)
  - Wayne County (Box 41)
    (Mrs. Mary Piscopink)
- Criminal Files
  The Criminal files series (9 linear feet) contains correspondence related the imprisonment and parole of prisoners Tuttle sentenced. The judge wrote letters to the parole board containing fairly frank assessments of whether a given criminal was a "very bad man" or simply a young person who had fallen into bad company. Tuttle also worked to secure employment for prisoners he had sentenced, once they had been released from prison, if they asked for help. These files also contain social statistics Tuttle kept as to the defendants' nationality, age, family status, and previous offenses.
  - 1912-1923
    (Pardon Atty, James A. Finch, Presidents Boards of Parole Heber H. Votaw, D.S. Dickerson, M.C. Duehay, Detroit U.S. Attorney John E. Kinnane, Clyde I. Webster)
    - Anonymous (Box 42)
    - A-Miscellaneous (Box 42)
    - Albright, George (Box 42)
      (car theft)
    - Allen, Fred (Box 42)
      (narcotics, treated in prison for tuberculosis)
    - Allen, Paul Hume (Box 42)
      (mail theft)
    - Anderson, C.H. (Box 42)
      (mailing harassing letters, 70 yrs old)
    - Anderson, James (Box 42)
      (narcotics)
    - B-Miscellaneous (Box 42)
    - Bagwell, Charles (Box 42)
      (car theft, photo of Iowa State Reformatory baseball team)
    - Bailey, John (Box 42)
    - Baltzley, Earl (Box 42)
      (Mann Act (commercialized vice))
    - Barnes, Orval D. (Box 42)
    - Basden, Almon (Box 42)
      (allowed to attend brother's funeral)
    - Bauer, Charles W. (Box 42)
    - Berg, Michael (Box 42)
    - Berry, Roy (Box 42)
    - Billingsly, Ora & Sherman (Box 42)
      (Liquor smuggling, appealed to 6th Circuit)
    - Bird, Charles (Box 42)
      (forgery)
    - Blake, Isaiah (Box 42)
      (theft from railcar)
    - Bookman, Jack (Box 42)
    - Bou, Anthony Vincent (Box 42)
      (forging whiskey labels)
    - Bowman, Fred C. (Box 42)
      (counterfeiting)
    - Brice, Walter (Box 42)
    - Brooks, Frank L. (Box 42)
      (oleomargarine law)
    - Brown, Glen D. (Box 42)
    - Burdo, Stanley (Box 42)
      (conscription act)
    - Burley, John (Box 42)
      (not stated)
    - C-Miscellaneous (Box 42)
    - Calhoun, Harry (Box 42)
    - Campbell, George H. (Box 42)
    - Carroll, Adrian (Box 42)
    - Casey, John M. (Box 42)
    - Cashill, David & John (Box 42)
    - Chaffee, Purl (Box 42)
    - Charlebois, Henry (Box 42)
    - Chisholm, Ralph (Box 42)
    - Church, Alton (Box 42)
      (refusing to register for the draft)
    - Clark, James M. (Box 42)
    - Clemens, Theodore (Box 42)
    - Clements, Joseph A. (Box 42)
      (receiving stolen car)
    - Coddington, Lucy (Box 42)
      (not given, pregnancy of inmate)
    - Cohen, Abe (Box 42)
    - Cole, Theodore E. (Box 42)
    - Collins, Neal J. (Box 42)
      (impersonating Federal officer, extortion)
    - Conception, John G. (Box 42)
      (not given, complaint of attorney misconduct)
    - Corea, Roy (Box 42)
    - Cory, Dan (Box 42)
    - Conklin, Fred (Box 42)
    - Conklin, Marie (Box 42)
    - Copper, Harry (Box 42)
    - Coy, Paul (Box 42)
    - Criner, Cecil & Ronnie L. (Box 42)
    - Czuzman, John (Box 42)
    - D-Miscellaneous (Box 42)
    - Daly, John (Box 42)
    - Davis, Ben (Box 42)
    - Day, Daniel (Box 42)
      (Volstead Act)
    - Deering, Edward A. (Box 42)
    - Delong, Stanley (Box 42)
    - Deminico, Louis (Box 42)
    - Denhoff, James (Box 42)
    - Dickey, Clyde (Box 42)
    - Dietrich, Edward S. (Box 42)
      (liquor)
    - Donnelly, John J. (Box 42)
    - Donahoe, Raymond P. (Box 42)
      (theft from railcars)
    - Donovan, Omar alias Otto Dressler (Box 42)
    - Dowar, Harry (Box 42)
    - Drbal, Myles (Box 42)
    - Dryden, William J. (Box 42)
      (mailing harassing and immoral letters)
    - Duncan, Charles O. (Box 42)
      (embezzlement)
    - DuRupau, Joseph J. (Box 42)
    - E-Miscellaneous (Box 42)
    - Easton, Louis D. (Box 42)
    - Edwards, George alias John Bulford (Box 42)
    - Elgin, Frank & Winnie (Box 42)
      (not given, inmate treated for Syphilis)
    - F-Miscellaneous (Box 42)
    - Faust, Thomas (Box 42)
      (coloring oleomargarine)
    - Fieron, W. Albert (Box 42)
      (not given, complaint about prisoner's property)
    - Fieron, Majick (Box 42)
      (espionage)
    - Fitzpatrick, William E. (Box 42)
    - Flaugh, Laura (Box 42)
    - Fletcher, Ross R. (Box 42)
    - Forbes, James A. (Box 42)
    - Foster, J.E. (Box 42)
      (not given)
    - Frank, Guy B. (Box 42)
    - Frederickson, Charles (Box 42)
    - G-Miscellaneous (Box 42)
    - Galbo, Joseph (Box 42)
      (leader of large gang of car thieves, Senator James Couzens)
    - Galloway, Lawrence W. (Box 42)
    - Gerard, Henry (Box 42)
      (mail fraud)
    - Glover, Charles (Box 42)
    - Gobay, Reginald (Box 42)
    - Godlewski, Joseph (Box 42)
    - Goetz, Edmund, Richard & Wilhelm (Box 42)
    - Graham, John William (Box 42)
    - Geiser, John (Box 42)
    - H-Miscellaneous (Box 42)
    - Hage, Allie (Box 42)
      (Mann Act, Assyrian citizen)
    - Halpin, William J. (Box 42)
    - Ham, Walter M. (Box 42)
      (theft, Senator William J. Harris)
    - Hamil, Albert J. (Box 42)
    - Hamilton, Marie (Box 42)
      (car theft, inmate's venereal disease)
    - Harper, Jack (Box 42)
      (car theft, British citizen)
    - Hass, Frederick (Box 42)
    - Hayward, Thomas W. (Box 42)
    - Henderson, Paul (Box 42)
    - Hendrickson, Ray R. (Box 42)
    - Hill, Warren (Box 42)
    - Hout, Winfred (Box 42)
      (theft)
    - Huether, Emil (Box 42)
    - Hughes, William (Box 42)
    - I-Miscellaneous (Box 42)
    - J-Miscellaneous (Box 42)
    - Jankowski, Peter (Box 42)
      (not given, prisoner's drawing of Tuttle)
    - Johnson, Charles (Box 42)
    - Jones, Johnny (Box 42)
    - Jones, Nile (Box 42)
      (Sec. 190)
    - K-Miscellaneous (Box 43)
    - Kirschoff, Albert (Box 43)
    - Koms, Louis (Box 43)
    - Kremsreiter, Joseph (Box 43)
      (sedition)
    - Kropis, Joseph (Box 43)
    - Kucel, Lawrence (Box 43)
    - Kuligiewicz, Albert (Box 43)
    - L-Miscellaneous (Box 43)
    - LaDell, Arthur alias Otto Fredericks (Box 43)
      (obscene mail)
    - LaGuerra, Louis (Box 43)
    - Landram, Warren Judd (Box 43)
    - Lapetina, Manuel (Box 43)
    - Larry, Gilbert (Box 43)
      (Car theft)
    - LaTour, George (Box 43)
      (leader of Chinese immigration smugglers)
    - Leach, Dr. H.M. (Box 43)
    - LeBeau, Theodore (Box 43)
    - Letinsky, Morris (Box 43)
    - Lewis, Wolf (Box 43)
    - Lindsey, Arthur D. (Box 43)
      (bank robbery)
    - Lindsay, Edward (Box 43)
    - Linn, Earl (Box 43)
    - Linville, Roy D. (Box 43)
    - Little, Arthur (Box 43)
    - Logan, Benjamin (Box 43)
    - Loewry, Aaron (Box 43)
    - Mc-Miscellaneous (Box 43)
    - MacDonald, E.A. (Box 43)
    - McFall, Jonathan (Box 43)
    - McGee, Albert Q. (Box 43)
    - McKee, Laurence Perry (Box 43)
    - McNamara, James (Box 43)
    - McWay, Arthur (Box 43)
      (fraud, Congressman Joseph W. Fordney)
    - M-Miscellaneous (Box 43)
    - Mairn, John (Box 43)
    - Maki, John J. (Box 43)
      (conversion of U.S. funds)
    - Maloff, Joseph (Box 43)
    - Maybee, Jack (Box 43)
    - Menge, Philip (Box 43)
      (perjury)
    - Meredith, Orlo L. (Box 43)
    - Meyers, Edward (Box 43)
    - Middleditch, John L. (Box 43)
      (mail theft, "simple-minded")
    - Miller, Leo (Box 43)
    - Miller, Robert (Box 43)
    - Miley, William (Box 43)
      (not given, instructions for filing habeas corpus)
    - Mitchell, William (Box 43)
    - Mley, John (Box 43)
    - Monett, Frank (Box 43)
    - Moore, William (Box 43)
    - Morton, Clyde (Box 43)